Anyway, just don't worry about it.
Okay.
Kobato.
Y-Yes sir...
With the window open all this time,
even someone as clueless as you
is bound to catch a cold.
But I...
I'm cold!
I'm sorry!
Really, it's still very cold, isn't it?
Yes, it's only the beginning of February, after all.
Speaking of which,
so many of the magazines at the convenience
store had features on chocolate!
I wonder if eating chocolate
makes you feel warm.
No, I think it's because
Valentine's Day is coming up.
Valentine's Day?
Kobato.
Dou sureba iin dakke?
Atarimae no kototte itsumo
Muzukashii na
Ureshii toki waratte
Suki na toki ni utaitai dake
Na no ni
Itsuka negai wa kanau to
Demo "itsuka" tte dore kurai?
Machikirenai yo
123! no aizu de ryoute hirogete
Zenshin ni hikari wo atsumete
Doko ni aru no?
Oshiete, watashi ni dekiru koto
Meippai kizu tsuite
Seiippai hashitte
Nan juu kai koronde naite
Sore de mo mada
Akireru kurai
Ashita wo shinjiteru
Yomogi Kindergarten
...The Travelers.
Fujimoto!
February fourteenth is Valentine's Day, right?!
What about it?
How about a Valentine's Day party
at Yomogi kindergarten?!
Why at the kindergarten?
Don't kindergartens have Valentine parties?
I'm sure some do, but in Japan,
that's a day for giving chocolates.
Yes. It also said so in a book.
So I thought, why not the kindergarten too?
What, the girls give chocolates to the boys?
What?
In Japan, it's the day girls give
chocolates to boys they like.
What?! Is that what Valentine's Day is?
Well, I understand nowadays
some boys give to girls too.
But there really is a lot you
don't know, isn't there?
To people you like...
What is it?
Why don't we give it a try?
A Valentine's Day party!
I mean, Ms. Sayaka...
She seems to be deep in thought again lately.
She's under a lot of stress,
but she pretends not to be.
I thought a Valentine's Day party
would cheer her up a bit.
But that's impossible.
The kindergarten financially can't afford
to be having parties these days.
That's not a problem!
B-Bakery Tirol will give us ingredients!
I went by this morning and
they said that I could work
for the ingredients needed to
make the chocolate!
Woah, calm down a bit.
Y-Yes.
So you're saying that you negotiated
with the bakery to work there
and in return the bakery will
pay us with ingredients
for everyone at the kindergarten
to make chocolate with.
U-Um. Did I say something wrong?
My schedule is full. I might not be
able to help out at the bakery.
And I just booked the evenings to work
late night at a construction site.
Oh, I'll be doing the work!
The owner told me that I could come in to
work for him every day after kindergarten,
until Valentine's Day.
But...
I'll be fine!
I, Kobato, will do my best for Valentine's Day!
Go, go, Kobato! Yah!
Okay then, you go for it.
Kobato wants to have a Valentine's Day
party at the kindergarten?
Yes.
She is such a sweet girl, Kobato.
Bakery Tirol
This Year's Chocolates
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you so much.
Please come again!
Thanks for your help.
Good work.
I've still got lots to do!
Yes, I would like to take you up on it,
but today, it's closing time.
Oh, is it that time already?
Um, um... Is there anything
else I can help you with?
There are two more days before
Valentine's Day. You're doing plenty.
Okay then would you please bring
in the sign from outside?
Yes sir! I'll be right back!
Hey! That hurt!
We keep falling upon the strangest places!
Huh?
Well at least we didn't fall in some place
like the middle of the ocean this time.
Yeah, that just about killed us!
Ioryogi-san?
Huh?
Wow, a girl! This world has people!
Hey!
We don't know yet if this is a world
where white buns like you speak!
Right...
Ioryogi-san?
Huh?
Umm... this guy's name is Kurogane.
And I'm Fay.
This is Syaoran, and this one over here is...
Huh?
Wh-What is it?
Uh, nothing.
Yes. I see.
Mocona, you can talk. It's okay.
This girl is not one bit surprised.
Sure. That's not the only talking
doll. Ioryogi-san talks too.
Ioryogi-san?
Kobato! Come on!
How long do you plan on staying out here?!
The shop owner's starting to get worried...
Ioryogi-san!
So you're Ioryogi-san!
I'm Mocona. How do you do?
Hey, I know you! You're from
that amusement park!
Are you traveling?
Yeah.
A four person journey?
Three persons and one Mocona!
One Mocona?
That's how you count Moconas.
In that case... Ioryogi-san would
count as one Ioryogi-san?
That's wrong! How could you even think that?!
You were right! Kuro-sama and
Ioryogi-san sound alike!
We do not!
You do.
I think you do.
In this world, Kurogane is small and blue.
Shut up, white bun!
Hey, don't you try to get away from me!
So you're visiting on a trip?
Something like that.
Hey, don't you try to get away from me!
I read in a book that when you're on a journey,
you stay in a number of places.
You can't catch me!
I read in a book that when you're on a journey,
you stay in a number of places.
Have you decided where you're staying tonight?
No, not yet.
It would be nice to have a place to stay.
But we don't have any of this world's money.
You don't have any money?
We have money, but I doubt
that they accept it here.
That's a problem.
Well, but there aren't any girls traveling with us,
so I guess we could camp outside.
I'm a girl!
How do you differentiate your gender? By color?
By cuteness.
Huh?
Um, if you need a place...
Uh...
You're welcome to stay with us!
I knew it.
B-But...
No problem at all! We have a room!
Oh, but we only have one futon!
But we could all bundle up and sleep together!
Oh, but you're not all small.
We can separate the top futon from the bottom
futon and we can cover ourselves with those!
You only have one futon? Then you live alone?
No! I live with Ioryogi-san!
Well then all the more!
It will be fine! Really!
Let's take her up on it. Uh...
I'm Kobato Hanato!
Nice to meet you, Kobato!
Hey! You guys!
Whatever happens, you will protect Kobato.
Right, Ioryogi-san?
You...
Anyway, let's go! To Kobato's house!
Go!
Yes, let's go!
Off we go!
Is this really okay?
I'm sure he's got something figured out.
Kuro-tan!
Why do you look so put off?
Oops, I made a mistake!
On second thought, he probably has
nothing figured out! That goofball!
I'm late!
It's the kindergarten's day off today.
I've got to work at Bakery Tirol this morning!
Oh, no! What am I going to do!
Oh no! What shall I do? What shall I do?
We tried to wake you up a number of times.
You were in a deep sleep, Kobato.
Nothing changes with you, does it?
Even with all these people in your room.
I'm sorry!
Um, I'm going out, but please stay if
you wish. Make yourselves at home.
Kobato, you're going to the bakery, right?
Yes! To work!
And, uh... They're going to give you ingredients
to make chocolates for Valentine's Day.
That's right.
In that case, we'll help, too.
Huh?
Great idea! For putting us up last night.
Let's see.
Syaoran, you go with her to the bakery.
What?!
You're good at cooking.
Besides, Kuro-sama just doesn't
fit the image of a cake shop?
Don't even ask me. I refuse.
Kuro-tan and I will work somewhere else.
To get some money.
What?
Mocona will...
I'm staying with Ioryogi-san!
Why's that?
I'm starting to like you.
The feeling's not mutual!
So let's get going. We have
a big day ahead of us.
Yeah!
Come on, Ioryogi-san, yeah!
Ah?
Team work between those that get along.
We don't get along!
Oh Ioryogi-san is jealous because I'm so cute.
I'm not jealous!
Yumi, who's the boy?
Oh, apparently someone Kobato knows.
I'm pretty good at pretending to be a stuffed doll.
Hey, stop talking!
This is awesome! Syaoran, you're
really good with your hands.
It's just a matter of getting used to.
I keep practicing, but I can never
get packaged so nicely.
Don't try to stuff it all in at once.
A bit at a time, like this.
A bit at a time...
I did it!
Don't sing, either!
Syaoran, you people have been
traveling for a long time, right?
Yes, but it's not a journey with a destination.
Is that so?
I guess you could say our destination
is to continue traveling.
Um...
Then it's undecided where you're going?
It would be difficult to decide.
For one thing, we don't know how
long we can stay in one place.
But...
I have someone waiting for me.
Someone waiting for you?
Waiting for me, without ever
knowing when I'll be home next.
There's a place...
A place I want to go to.
No matter what.
That place...
You want to go there because there's
meaning in you going there,
or because there's someone there
that you want to see?
Someone... to see...
Someone that I want to see...
We sure worked a lot!
We just sat there!
Yes, we worked as poster Moconas!
What the heck is that?
Welcome home!
How were things at the Bakery?
We're home. Syaoran really is a good worker.
The shop owner was very impressed.
Oh, well...
Though he seemed to think that your
clothes were a bit unusual.
Oh, clothes. Yeah, here too.
We were asked if we were
going to a costume party.
You then complicated things when you said,
"I wonder if people look at this
as costume play in this world?"
Anyway, here.
It's only one day's worth, so it isn't much.
But, but... are you sure?
Yes. You would make us happy by accepting.
It's for putting us up last night.
Thank you very much! I will use
it for the kindergarten.
What, already?
What is it?
We have to go to the next world.
Whenever this accessory shines.
What?!
Thank you for letting us stay.
It was only for one night and two days,
but I really had a good time!
Thank you for your hospitality.
Oh no, I hardly did anything.
I'm sorry I couldn't do more.
Hey, Kobato is...
Right?
But...
She's become quite unstable.
Wow. It's a very beautiful light.
Isn't it? I'm quite fond of it.
The best that those from a different
world can do is watch over her.
It becomes a light at night.
The best that those from a different
world can do is watch over her.
Quite convenient, actually.
The best that those from a different
world can do is watch over her.
It really is. That's wonderful.
The best that those from a different
world can do is watch over her.
It really is. That's wonderful.
That includes us.
But you barely notice it during the day.
Take good care of her.
Oh, what a waste.
You don't have to tell me. I know.
You want one too, Kobato?
I sure would! How can I get one?!
I hope you get there.
To the place you want to go.
Thank you very much.
Those people...
They're from another world.
Ningenkai's not the only world, after all.
There's Tenkai, Chikai, Ikai... and there
could be numerous other worlds as well.
I hope that next time,
Syaoran and his friends will arrive at the world
where the person waiting for him lives.
Valentine's Day Party
Let's do our best
They're all having so much fun.
Yes.
Kobato really worked hard for this, didn't she?
Well, yes.
Kobato, that's got a funny shape!
What is it supposed to be?
I was trying to make a star.
Looks more like a starfish.
Huh, a starfish?!
Aside from the chocolate,
she also gave me some money.
So I was able to get wrapping
paper and cards, too.
I hope she didn't work herself too hard.
Hey Yoshio, who are you going to give your
chocolates to?
My Mom and Dad, and my little sister.
I'm giving mine to my Mommy.
And if you'd like, I can give you one too, Kobato.
Thank you very much.
I think on Valentine's Day you should give your
best chocolate to your favorite person.
Kobato, who are you going
to give your best one to?
Me?
Kobato better have saved some for me too.
What is it now?
Kobato.
Seriously, you're running out of time.
Nakushita mono to
Atsumeta mono no hazama ni
Anata no egao ochiteita no
Todokisou de todokanai
Tonde yukeru wake janai shi
Warawasete agetai dake na no ni,
Yaku tatazu no kono tsubasa
Nan no tame ni aru no darou?
Anata no soba de warau yo,
Watashi ni dekiru koto
Atatameru dake de mo ii no kana
Semete tsutsumitai
Kizuku no, sono tame no tsubasa to
Ima koso watashi warau yo
Next episode
...Footsteps of Spring.
Ima koso watashi warau yo
Next episode
...Footsteps of Spring.